Department of Government Records, ca. 1920-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Department of Government Records
ca. 1920-[ongoing]
Smith College. Dept. of Government.
RG 52 UUID:3e309cdd-a4bd-4fe3-b68c-e2cb36594250
1 box (1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in one box and contains course syllabi, mid-year and final exam questions, black and white photographs, news releases, and department announcements.
Historical Note
In 1919, Smith College established the History and Government Department. By 1921, the department's name changed to the Government Department.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Department records, 1880s, 1920s-1990s, contain materials describing the department's courses and activities. Types of materials include course syllabi, mid-year and final exam questions, black and white photographs of students and faculty, news releases, and department announcements.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
History of the Collection
The Government Department records were created by the departments and its students and transferred/donated to the College Archives.
Additional Information
Related Material
Researchers should also view: RG 42. Faculty
- General 1995, undated material (Box 1159, Folder 1)
- Courses- 11-412b 1964-66 (Box 1159, Folder 2)
- Courses- American Political Parties 1953 (Box 1159, Folder 3)
- Courses- General 1948, 1952-53, 1972-73 (Box 1159, Folder 4)
- Courses- Government 11 1938-39, 1945-47 (Box 1159, Folder 5)
- Courses- 21-40 1925-58 (Box 1159, Folder 6)
- Courses- 100-230a, 310b-342a 1935-63, 1977-78 (Box 1159, Folder 7)
- Courses- 42b-45 1945-58 (Box 1159, Folder 8)
- Courses- Studies in Local Government- photos 1970 (Box 1159, Folder 9)
- Courses- Studies in Local Government- photos 1971 (Box 1159, Folder 10)
- Elections 1930, 1940s, 1956 (Box 1159, Folder 11)
- Elections- Mock Republican Conventions 1968 (Box 1159, Folder 12)
- International Relations Group 1940 (Box 1159, Folder 13)
- Lecture notes-students 1880s (Box 1159, Folder 14)
- Lectures 1936-39, 1994 (Box 1159, Folder 15)
- Outlines, assignments, reading lists 1920s-30s (Box 1159, Folder 16)
- Speakers 1995 (Box 1159, Folder 17)
- Student information 1954 (Box 1159, Folder 18)
- Summer Intern Program 1963, undated material (Box 1159, Folder 19)
- Photographs 1940s-60s, 1980s (Box 1159, Folder 20)